Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
I didn't know you very well.
We only knew each other
for a short time,
but it was a really nice time.
That period of time
we spent together,
it was a really nice time.
Oh, my God. It's fucking over.
It's over. It's over.
It's over. It's over!
It's fucking over!
I'm fucking dying.
You don't get it.
You don't understand!
I'm not fucking crazy.
I'm not crazy!
Please understand,
I'm not crazy.
We had a time.
We had a time,
but it's over now.
There's no tomorrow.
I'm not fucking crazy!
Hi, how's the new house?
It's good.
I think it's so great
that you own a house.
This is the best thing
you could have done.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. It's... Hello?
Wait, did you just say
something? 'Cause I can't...
Can you come over?
Ugh, I can't.
I'm supposed to go to my
sister-in-law's birthday party,
but I really don't want to go.
I just really want to
stay at home
because she
fucking hates me.
Okay.
What did you just say?
Hold on. Are you
speaking into the phone?
I can barely hear you.
Are you okay?
Not really.
Oh, shit, Amy.
I'll come over, if I can, okay?
Okay.
Look, just pause.
Don't do anything
you might regret.
Go for a walk or why don't you
try watching a movie?
A movie's an hour and a half.
I heard hour and... what?
An hour and a half... what?
Are you laying down and
talking into the phone?
Hello? I cannot understand you.
Can you talk into the phone?
Oh, my gosh. Wait, I'm getting
a text from my brother, now.
Bring salad? Bring... I don't
even want to go to this party.
I'm just terrible
at making salads.
Look, they sprang this stuff
on me at the last second
and she doesn't even like me
when I go over there.
She's just mean to me. I don't
know... I don't know what I did.
Fuck.
Amy?
Amy!
Hey, Jane.
What is going on?
Come on down from there.
I was thinking...
I could be made
into a leather jacket.
This used to be alive.
And now I just walk on it
and don't even think twice.
But in death, it
becomes useful, you know?
I want to be useful in death.
Here, drink that.
I don't want that.
But I am telling you
because I want you
to make sure it happens
when I die.
You are going to die
if you keep relapsing.
That's not what's happening.
But I am drinking, so that's...
technically a relapse.
Yeah, but...
it doesn't matter.
Tell me you'll take care of it.
Nobody is turning you
into a leather jacket.
You're not making sense.
You're not thinking straight
because you are loaded.
Look at me.
I...
am going to die tomorrow.
- No, you're not.
- Yes, I am.
It's okay.
No, you're not.
It's not okay.
It just is.
So...
Tomorrow is another day.
I can't sit here and
watch you get wasted.
I won't be held hostage.
So, I am going to leave
and you're going to
call me tomorrow.
There is no tomorrow for me.
I have to let go, oh, my God.
You know this.
There's a guy
in Denmark.
He's a leather worker, I want...
No. Stop.
Goodbye.
Hmm?
Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Was I dreaming?
So, this is gonna be
the spare bedroom,
but I have to
finish wallpapering.
'Cause the previous owners
had it this sort of
babyish blue nursery color.
Extra storage.
Good to have.
And this is the bedroom...
That's a big TV.
What, about 50 inches?
I don't know, it was
the previous owners.
They just left that TV?
Yeah.
You wanna watch something?
I don't know if it works.
You
haven't tried to turn it on?
No.
I don't really watch TV.
Fair enough.
That's a big bed.
You know, I actually
do really regret
not going to Majorca
one summer
because I was trying to
win over an ex-girlfriend.
Oh, that's sad.
I had the whole thing
planned out.
That's actually a tragedy.
That's a true regret,
if we're being honest.
That's bad.
What about you?
How you doing
in the regret department?
- Truth only.
- Okay.
Um...
Go.
I regret not knowing
how to make an omelet.
I wouldn't say that's a regret.
I mean, I've tried really hard
and failed really hard.
Okay, fine. Next.
Skip.
It just takes a very tiny
amount of my brain space,
but it's something.
I terminated a pregnancy
when I was 22.
Terminated?
I mean, I had an abortion.
I know, just the term.
I didn't really...
I hadn't thought about it
until I bought this house.
You hadn't thought about...
what, the kid?
Well, it's not a kid.
It's a bunch of cells
in my uterus, but...
Um...
Yeah, I hadn't
thought about the kid
until I bought the house.
Do you regret it?
Don't answer that.
No, I don't.
I don't regret it. I mean,
I probably wouldn't have
been able to buy this house
if I'd had it.
I don't know why
I'm reacting like this.
No, I don't regret it.
What do you say we
figure out that TV, now?
Sorry.
What? I thought you said
you were gonna
bring the salad?
I know, but if I come,
I'm just gonna be distracted
and I just want to sit
and play with these ideas.
You know I can't control
when inspiration strikes.
I'm just gonna annoy Susan,
anyway.
Look, I'll take you guys
to dinner tomorrow,
or whenever.
Tell Susan I said
happy birthday, okay?
Of course, I will.
Will you call me tomorrow?
Yeah, okay. Love you, bye.
Oh, no way.
No, no, hold it. Hold it.
Got it.
Wow.
Wow, this is...
Amy, are you there?
Goddammit, unlock the door.
All right. Amy, I'm really
freaking out right now
because all that stuff
you were saying earlier.
What were you talking about?
And I can't...
Like, now,
I don't know where you are
or what is going on.
Amy?
Hey, it's Amy.
Leave a message
or text if it's important.
Yeah, hi, uh...
I feel like you put this idea
of dying in my head
and now I'm paranoid and
you're not calling me back.
Can you just call me back?
And I broke in your house.
We're on vacation in the Keys.
It's gorgeous
and I'm in the water.
I got the snorkel gear on.
- We were on one of those
- You okay?
- snorkel tours...
- I'm fine.
and she refuses
to get in the water.
- She wouldn't come in.
- No, I'm telling you,
you guys,
dolphins are down to fuck.
- Oh, God, here we go.
- DTF all the time.
This is her new kick, okay?
I'm curious
what you think of it.
I am obsessed
with the idea that...
Are you expecting someone?
No, I'm not expecting anyone.
Did you get me a stripper
this year?
I should have done that.
Baby, one year
you have to get me a stripper!
He always threatens it...
Hey.
I thought you weren't coming.
No, but then I decided to come.
Okay.
I missed you.
Oh, I missed you, too.
- No, I missed...
- You okay?
Yeah. No, I'm good. I'm good.
Oh, you put these up.
Yeah. Well, we love
what you do. We love you.
- I love you, too.
- Why are you in your pajamas?
Yes. Well, they're floral.
I don't want to go in.
Is your wrist okay?
I gotta go see Madison.
- I got to go see Madison.
- Madison's sleeping.
- She's always happy to see me.
- Yes, but she's sleeping.
- What happened to your wrist?
- I don't know. I don't know.
Hi, Susan.
Hello, Jane.
It's her birthday, so.
Happy... Happy birthday.
She just... She came.
Yes, I can see.
It's Jane.
Jane is here, everyone.
Jane, I'm so happy
you could make it.
Thought inspiration struck.
Let's go in and say hi
to everybody. Okay?
- I'll go say hi.
- You're just in time for cake.
I do. I love...
I love cake.
Awesome, we're gonna have some.
She loves cake.
This is Jane.
I told you about
Brian and Tilly?
- Hi.
- Have a seat.
Susan was just
telling us about
her fascination
with dolphin fucking.
Oh, where you going? Sit down.
Take a seat. It's cool.
Anyways,
yes, dolphins are
like sex maniacs.
You guys, I'm not kidding you.
Dolphins.
They will fuck all the time.
They fuck around
with porpoises,
with baby dolphins...
Sometimes they'll just kill it.
- I mean, it's wild!
- Oh, my gosh!
They've been known
to trap other dolphins in caves
to rape them.
I can't even!
Do you know,
I just read the other day
that they will
bump into puffer fish
because they'll get high.
You can get high from
bumping into a puffer fish.
Wow. That's a new fun fact
that I haven't heard.
I knew their dicks
could grab things,
but I didn't know they
get high off of puffer fish.
You love that.
No, they get high
- off of bumping into things?
- Yes!
Yes, I'm saying that dolphins,
they are, pretty much,
just like us.
Oh, Susan!
They are!
Okay, I'm sorry, that's
not exactly what I want
and how I want to
live my life,
but we have similarities.
Right? It's human nature.
Doesn't, Michael Jackson have
that song called Human Nature?
Yes, he does. Madonna...
And Boyz II Men.
Love Boyz II Men.
Actually, I think
it's really interesting,
about the dolphins.
I like you. She's great.
She's great, Brian. Good job.
Yeah, she's great.
I didn't realize dolphins
were so interesting.
I know. I know!
They are really humans
without society.
- Jane?
- Yes?
What's your take on
the whole dolphin-fucking thing
and how we're
not so different than fish?
- Uh...
- No, baby,
dolphins are not fish.
Okay, so Jane and I
very rarely agree on anything,
but I actually think
we might be
on the same page on this one.
You spend all your days
looking deep
into your microscope,
looking at these
small images saying,
"Oh, this flower
is a universe,"
and I'm just saying that
dolphins are human-like
and we're all the same, right?
We're all the same.
Humans are the only animal
or creature that
pretends to be what it's not.
Albert Camus said that,
I think. I Googled it.
- I like that quote.
- That's a good one.
- Thank you, Jane.
- Wow, we have a reader.
She's something, huh?
She is.
I just...
We're all gonna die.
I just think we should be able
to talk about it, right?
I mean, I'm dying to know.
She's funny, right?
- Wow.
- No, she's joking.
- She's just joking around.
- You don't have to humor her.
- You're joking.
- Well,
it's like, I just
have this feeling,
the way that you know
when you're about to
get a cold the next day
and it just hasn't hit yet?
I know that's
what is happening.
I'm going to die tomorrow.
But how do you know?
I don't know. I just know.
So, you know it
or you don't know it?
Well, I know that I don't know.
but I know
I don't want to be alone
and I know that I'm
going to die tomorrow.
- Well, if you...
- I know
that I'm going to
die tomorrow.
But you don't know.
I know that I'm
going to die tomorrow.
I know that I'm going to die.
Okay, great. So,
you don't know, right?
I know that it's my birthday
and I want to talk about
dolphin fucking.
It's all I want to talk about
tonight.
I don't want to
talk about death
because I am
not that old yet.
Okay. You know what?
Why don't I go into the kitchen
to get that special thing
for the birthday girl?
No, no, don't go now, Jason.
Just stay, now.
What?
Go get my cake.
I'm gonna go get the cake.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, Susan. It's just...
something's just terribly wrong
and I just have to say it.
I'm going to die tomorrow.
I'm dying.
Jane, we heard you.
- I'm dying.
- I heard you! Okay?
You are doing
what you always do,
which is make everything
about you.
It's all about you, Jane,
all the fucking time.
You sit alone
in that room of yours
taking pictures
of God knows what,
because you can't hold
a normal fucking job.
The only reason I tolerate you
is to make Jason happy.
And I pray to God,
every fucking day,
that my sweet daughter
does not have
whatever gene this is
that makes you this way.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- I just thought for a second,
- ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
when the lights went out,
that that was it.
- Do you know? Is that it?
- ♪ Happy birthday, dear Susan ♪
- Did we... I think that it...
- ♪ Happy birthday to you. ♪
Are we already dead?
Did Jason ever tell you
about the time that we had to
take her on vacation with us?
Uh-huh. Yeah.
She didn't want
to be left alone,
- so we took her. She got lost.
- It's okay.
I feel that way all the time,
like I'm going to die tomorrow
and I got to get
everything done today.
No. I know.
That feeling is
just paralyzing.
But it's really gonna happen
for me.
What are you talking about?
You don't know that.
Yeah, I do. I know it.
I mean, just like I know
if I drop this,
it's going to break.
For fuck's sake, Jason!
Mom?
I know she's your sister,
but she has got to go!
Mom?
Get the fuck away from me,
Jane!
Jane, man.
She's crazy, right?
I don't think she's that crazy.
She could be right.
What?
I mean, consider for a second
that she's right.
We all have to die
at some point.
Why not tomorrow?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Do you want to get a drink
somewhere else?
Yes, I do.
Just say, for instance,
that Jane is right.
Why are you always
making excuses for your sister?
Just listen to me.
I listened to you about
dolphin fucking.
Just listen.
Fine.
We're all gonna die
at some point.
Yeah, no shit.
We are going to die.
I'm gonna die.
I could die tomorrow.
I'm gonna die tomorrow.
Susan? Susan?
- Susan! Susan!
- Oh, God, I'm gonna die.
I need to go to the hospital.
I love you, Pop.
- Hey.
- Mom?
- It's okay.
Dad?
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, everything's
gonna be okay.
Why are you crying?
It's okay, it's okay.
Are you drunk?
Yes, a little bit.
I'm gonna die tomorrow.
And so is your dad.
I should have done this
for him sooner.
I was waiting for him to die
to break up with you.
I mean, I was gonna
give it three months.
I didn't want to be an asshole.
We weren't gonna last anyway.
I don't want to die. Mom!
Mom, I don't want to die now.
She did this to us.
Who?
Your sister.
Not only is she killing us,
she's killing her.
She's killing Madison.
What do you wanna do?
You know.
Okay.
There's no nd
to leave a message.
Amy, please, call me back.
What the hell is that message?
What are you talking about?
I know you know
what is going on
and you've left me
all alone with this.
Please. Amy, please, please!
You're my friend, call me back.
Hey, it's Amy.
I won't be around tomorrow.
Or any day after that, but
feel free to leave a message.
Hey, it's Amy.
I won't be around tomorrow.
Or any day after that, but
feel free to leave a message.
There's no need
to leave a message.
All right, let's do it!
Do I have to wear the helmet?
Uh, yeah. Definitely very
important to wear the helmet.
You know, these things
look like big toys,
but at the end of the day,
if you hit anything too fast
and too straight on,
this thing can flip
right the fuck over.
Well, I'm gonna die anyway.
I mean...
not here. I mean,
not on my watch.
Right.
But I'm definitely gonna
die tomorrow.
Umm...
I can't hear anything.
Okay.
But I'm dying tomorrow.
Please.
Look...
I don't think that
anything is wrong with you,
but if you're worried about
catching something,
I could easily give you
some antibiotics or...
No, I don't need antibiotics.
You know when you're
on a highway, you know,
and there's a semi
truck up ahead of you
and you know, I have to
speed up and get past that
before something
really bad happens?
That's what's going on.
Or when you're
walking in New York City...
Have you been to New York City?
Yes, I've been
to New York City.
Right, so in the summer,
when you look up
and there's air conditioners
everywhere, and...
you just know one of those
is going to pop out
and crash down on my head.
Or like, when you lock up
everything at night,
I mean, you make sure
everything's locked,
but then
you just know something
really bad is gonna happen.
And then you lay down
finally to go to sleep,
but then you imagine this guy,
and his friends,
and they're coming...
not just to take
everything that you have,
but to rape you, and kill you.
And not just rape you,
but taunt you
so, kind of, mercilessly
that you're going to have to
beg for your own...
Do you ever ride a dune buggy?
No.
- You want to?
- Yes.
We could go now,
you can make a U-turn.
That's actually on
the schedule for tomorrow.
Oh, there's a schedule,
that's very fun.
A lot of people don't think
schedules are fun,
but I'm glad to hear
you think they are,
because to me,
that's a big part of my life.
We're in.
Hey.
Good job.
This place is nice.
Wow.
So, this is
your brother's place?
Yeah, but he never uses it.
It's great
Back door,
in case of an emergency.
It's good to know your exits.
I thought about buying
a place out here like this,
but I don't know,
it felt too isolated.
I like being isolated.
I don't think
you have a choice,
'cause you
don't have any friends.
That's not very nice.
What's wrong
with being isolated?
Nothing.
You know, I know you said
you didn't like TV,
so I went ahead and removed
all of the televisions,
in fact,
all the entertainment options,
so it's just you and me.
That's perfect.
You mind if I get more wine?
No, of course not.
No? I don't want to make you
uncomfortable if you...
That's fine,
just 'cause I don't drink
doesn't mean you shouldn't.
Can't argue with that.
Are those for show or
do people actually shoot?
We can shoot them.
Do you like guns?
Yeah.
You wanna shoot some bottles?
No.
I don't like guns.
Well, you don't have to.
We can take that off schedule.
Free up some time.
To do what?
Usually when I come out here,
I just eat a bunch
of mushrooms.
Oh.
I'd do mushrooms.
Yeah?
Just not alcohol.
Okay.
I like that. You like that?
Uh, do you have any eights?
Go fish.
Do you have any fives?
You got a lot?
You gotta have a five
in there, somewhere.
- I don't. Go fish.
- Oh, my God.
Um, do you have any eights?
Did I just ask you that?
I can't remember.
Do you feel anything?
Mmm... I guess colors
are a little bit brighter.
But I don't, like,
see anything.
Do you feel anything?
Um...
I'm seeing a bunch of diamonds
and hearts on these cards.
I see them, too.
- Pizza!
- I'll get it.
Don't cheat.
I have extra cash
if you need it.
Is everything okay?
Craig.
Pizza!
Is everything okay?
What's wrong?
November 25th.
The day after tomorrow?
What do we have to leave
a day early or something?
It's fine.
It's fine, everything's fine.
Want some pizza?
I can't believe it.
I know.
You wanna make out?
Okay.
Ah, I can't do this right now.
Fuck.
You just think like,
where am I gonna hide?
Everything's closet space.
I should have
built a tunnel
or like a lock or something.
It's not really my specialty,
but I could...
I could refer you to...
I could refer you
to a psychologist.
It's just not really
my specialty.
You all right?
It's just, you're
really handsome and I...
- What is it?
- Excuse me.
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
Wait, wait.
What's happening?
Oh, God, I don't know.
What is it? Can I help?
Oh! Oh, God!
Oh!
Shh, shh.
My mother always
used to hum to me,
would you hum
something for me?
- Like that?
- Mm, yes, yes.
Yes, exactly.
I...
I need to...
I need to go be with my wife.
You need to...
Go!
Hi.
Oh, hello.
No.
No, I missed you.
I miss you all the time.
Taken a long time...
Is this how it ends?
I just came back
to see if this is real.
If you were real.
I still don't know
if it's real.
I didn't know you very well.
We only knew each other
for a short time.
It was a really nice time.
That period of time
that we spent together.
It was a really...
nice time.
What are you doing?
The sunrise.
It's beautiful.
Do you feel different?
After what we did?
No.
No, I don't.
Are you mad at me?
What do you think?
Okay.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
- Right?
- Yeah.
I'll go make us some tea.
I'm not mad at you.
Kinda mad at myself
for staying in
this relationship for...
I don't know, six months
past its expiration date.
You didn't even show up
to my birthday party.
My dad had a stroke.
Yeah, I understand.
I just feel like if you
were really into me,
you would have, like,
texted to say
you weren't coming.
We can stop
talking about this now.
Should we wake her up?
I don't know.
No.
It's better it happens
in her sleep.
All the stupid things
they used to talk about.
Stupid things
to be interested in.
It was a waste of time.
I liked those stupid things
you said.
Should I open my presents?
Yeah.
I just wanted to
connect to someone.
Or something.
Who do you think lives here?
It doesn't matter.
Platypus, platypus
it's always so fucking cute.
It's so cute.
Hi, I'm Jane.
I'm dying.
Hi.
I'm Sky.
I'm dying too.
Hi, I'm Erin.
I'm dying, too.
Hey, can I swim in that pool?
Do you think these ants
are gonna die?
Of course.
Everything is.
Who's mowing their lawn
right now?
I think I just got my period.
It's my last...
It's my last period.
The women back in the day
used to sit in the streams.
And the streams would
take away all the blood.
- For like the whole...
- Tribe.
And the women would get their
period at the same time, too.
And, like, so when
the Spaniards came
and would see
the rivers of blood,
they would think, "Oh,
they're doing sacrifices."
Weirdest thing.
I love trees.
I'm gonna miss them.
I'm gonna miss trees, too.
Excuse me?
Um...
Do you do custom work?
Like, if I were to bring you...
a...
a mammal, could you
make a leather jacket for me?
I can assume that
you know the smell of death
takes a while.
It's something that you learn.
We do do custom work.
You have to bring in the skin
as soon as possible.
It can't be rotting.
And ideally, it would be good
if it was warm.
- Okay?
- Uh-huh.
If you bring the carcass in
and it's still warm,
I can skin it,
and then I will cure
it using a salt solution.
When the salt solution is done,
I will then take the hide and
hang it out in the sun to dry.
It's a very long process.
And it's up to you
to bring in the hide
in the proper condition.
Do you understand?
Uh-huh.
If you bring it in that way, we
can make you whatever you like.
What do you do
with the rest of the body?
I'm okay.
I'm ready.
I'm not okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
I'm not okay.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org